electronics-expo.com 2011-09-18

# Electronics-Expo.com - The best brands in Electronics at the best prices - Safe and Secure Online Shopping

## Electronics Expo Online Privacy Policy

This is the online privacy policy of Electronics-Expo.com, a division of Electronics Expo, LLC. You can reach us by mail at 70 Demarest Dr, Wayne, NJ 07470, by telephone at (973) 808-8838 or e-mail us at privacy@electronics-expo.com. Please remember that this site and the servers that make this site available are located in the U.S. and hosted by Electronics Expo. By using this site you agree to the transfer, collection, processing and use of data by this site. The content on our site may include, among other items of interest, information on our company and the products well sell, our advertising, entertainment and opportunities to shop online. We may also offer opportunities to apply for employment. 

## Secure Online Ordering Information

The Electronics Expo store offers products available for purchase online, by phone or because of manufacturer distribution policies, certain product may be only available at our retails stores. Customers must be over age 18 with a valid credit card. When you place an order for product online from the Electronics-Expo.com Internet store or request a catalog online, we collect information associated with the transaction. This information includes your name, mailing address, products ordered, and credit card information. We ask for this information so that we may fulfill the order request. 

Your online credit card transactions are secure at Electronics-Expo.com. We use Secure Socket Layering (SSL), the industry-standard encryption technology that ensures safe Internet transmission of your personal information. When the letters "http" in the URL change to "https," the "s" indicates you are in a secure area employing SSL; also, your browser may give you a pop-up message that you're about to enter a secure area. 

Making a credit card purchase is just as safe on our Web site as it is by telephone, but if you prefer the latter, you may purchase online merchandise by calling toll-free 1.888.707.EXPO from Monday thru Friday, 10am to 6pm ET. One of our sales associates will gladly take your order. (Our offices are closed on National Holidays) 

You will have to register with Electronics-Expo.com to place your online order. For those who register, we will capture your login name (e-mail address), password, name and mailing address, alternate ship-to addresses, and credit card information. When a registered person returns to the site to place subsequent orders, they can identify themselves with login name (e-mail address) and password. 

## Information We Collect Online

This information will be used by Electronics-Expo.com, members of the Electronics-Expo family and/or our technical and fulfillment departments to help provide products and services that meet our customer's needs. Electronics Expo may share your information with certain third parties to perform services on our behalf. When you place an online order, we will send a confirming e-mail message. You will also be contacted if upon completion of your on-line order, the item you are buying is being shipped to an address other than your billing address. This is done in order to prevent shipping to purchases made with a stolen credit card. Address Verification will be required. (For additional information on Address Verification please check out the Customer Service Section of this site.) In the future, we may also send an occasional e-mail featuring a special promotion or product that may be of interest to our customers. Any customer who prefers not to receive an online order confirmation may "opt-out" by so indicating this preference on the order form. If you do receive an e-mail from us that you would rather not receive, simply follow the "opt-out" instructions included in the e-mail. 

When you place an order online, we add your name and address to our print catalog mailing list. If you do not wish to receive our mailings, you can send the mailing label from the catalog to the following address: 

**Electronics Expo, LLC.**  
Attn: Mailing Changes  
70 Demarest Dr  
Wayne, NJ 07470 

If you have recently moved, or are planning a move in the near future, you should let us know of the change of address and we'll be sure to update our records. For all mailing questions and changes, please call 1.888.707.EXPO, or send the information to Electronics-Expo at the address shown above. 

We use "cookie" technology (where our servers deposit special codes on a visitor's computer) to track the total number of visitors to each of our sites in an aggregate form. We do not automatically extract personally identifiable information in this process. The "cookie" technology will only be used to track non-personal information such as type of browser, operating system, and domain names to customize the website for each visitor and to improve the visitor's online experience. 

In some instances, when contact information has been provided by the visitor, and the visitor is 18 or older and has indicated that he/she would like to receive communications from us, we may send notices to visitors, usually in the form of an e-mail. These notices, may be sent periodically, will announce website upgrades, new product information, promotions and other similar updates that may be of interest to the visitor. Our mailers and other notices tell the visitor how to "opt-out" so that he or she can stop the notices at any time. 

For our internal purposes, we gather date, time, pages visited, originating search engine, and IP address of all visitors to our site. We keep this information for our internal security audit log, systems administration purpose, to help diagnose problems with our server(s), and to better administer our web site. 

You always have the right to request that contact information regarding you be deleted from our database. To request deletion of your contact information in our database, please call 1.888.707.EXPO for more information. Upon proper identification, you may review the personal information we have collected about you, request deletion, or refuse to allow further collection or use by writing to us at the address above. 

We reserve the right to change this policy at any time by posting it on our web site.
